[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Java feature?",
        "option": ["Object-oriented", "Use of pointers", "Platform Independent", "Dynamic"],
        "correctAnswer": "Use of pointers",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "Which data type is used to create a variable that should store text?",
        "option": ["myString", "Txt", "string", "String"],
        "correctAnswer": "String",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What is the size of a 'byte' data type in Java?",
        "option": ["4 bits", "8 bits", "16 bits", "32 bits"],
        "correctAnswer": "8 bits",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which method must be implemented by all Java threads?",
        "option": ["start()", "run()", "stop()", "wait()"],
        "correctAnswer": "run()",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Which keyword is used to prevent inheritance of a class in Java?",
        "option": ["static", "final", "volatile", "private"],
        "correctAnswer": "final",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "What is the default value of a boolean variable in Java?",
        "option": ["true", "false", "null", "0"],
        "correctAnswer": "false",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Which of the following is used to find and fix bugs in Java programs?",
        "option": ["JVM", "JRE", "JDK", "JDB"],
        "correctAnswer": "JDB",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following is a reserved keyword in Java?",
        "option": ["array", "goto", "null", "Integer"],
        "correctAnswer": "goto",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What does the 'public' keyword in a method declaration mean?",
        "option": ["Method is accessible to the same class only", "Method is accessible to the package", "Method is accessible to all classes", "Method is accessible to the subclass"],
        "correctAnswer": "Method is accessible to all classes",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which operator is used to compare two values in Java?",
        "option": ["=", "==", "equals()", "!="],
        "correctAnswer": "==",
        "userAnswer": null,
        "visited": false
    }
]
